Previously on "desperate housewives"... We're making a mistake. These are nice people.
(在此前的“欲乱绝情妻”中...) 我们弄错了, 他们是好人
My money says one of them isn't.
我的钞票告诉我其中一个不是
How creepy is Mrs. Huber's sister?
Huber夫人的妹妹好古怪啊
Promises were made.
(诺言许下了)
I'm going to find out exactly what happened to her.
我会查明她到底发生了什么事
Marriages came undone.
(婚姻破裂了)
Gabrielle and I are about to start a family.
Gabrielle和我打算要个孩子了
Well, we're not negotiating my uterus.
生小孩的事没得商量
George, would you go out to dinner with me?
George, 你想和我一起吃晚饭吗?
You mean like a date?
你的意思是像约会那样?
A date?
约会?
Was denied.
(被否认了)
I absolutely did not do that thing you accused me of.
我绝对没做过你说的那件事
Martha Huber waited her whole life for something to happen to her, something exciting.
(Martha Huber一辈子都在等待 一些令她激动的事情发生在她身上)
As a child, she hoped to be kidnapped by a band of pirates.
(在孩提时代, 她希望被一群海盗绑架)
As a teenager, she dreamt of being discovered by a hollywood talent scout.
(在少女时期, 她希望被好莱坞的星探发掘)
As a young woman, she fantasized a handsome millionaire would sweep her off her feet.
(在她正值妙龄之时, 她幻想着有个 英俊的百万富翁会拜倒在她的石榴裙下)
But the years had flown by, and still nothing exciting had ever happened to Martha Huber.
(但是随着岁月的流逝, 依然没有 任何令她激动的事情发生)
Until the night she was murdered.
(直到她被谋杀的那晚)
Hello, Mrs. Huber.
你好, Huber夫人
Paul.
Paul
Let me give you a hand.
我来帮你吧
That's really not necessary.
不用了
I insist.
请让我来吧
In those last moments, it occurred to her in addition to being boring,
(在最后的时刻, 她意识到生活 不仅仅是单调乏味的)
Life could also be very cruel.
(也可以是很残酷)
Luckily for Mrs. Huber, death was far more merciful.
(对于Huber而言幸运的是 死亡要仁慈得多)
What do you think?
你怎么认为?
That's our missing woman, all right.
是失踪的那个女人
Oh, jeez. Didn't take the media long to get wind of this.
天啊. 媒体很快就会得到消息了
Make sure no one contaminates my crime scene.
确保没人破坏案发现场
Hey, little lady.
嗨, 女士
A lot of people are looking for you, you know that?
你知道吗, 一大群人在找你呢
Your face is going to be on the front page of every paper in this state.
你马上就要上这个州里所有报纸的头版了
How's that for exciting?
那样够刺激了吧?
Officer Jackson couldn't be sure, but for a brief moment,
(Jackson警官不敢肯定, 但在一瞬间)
he thought he saw the corpse of Martha Huber...
(他觉得他看到Martha Huber的尸体...)
smile.
(笑了)
Episode 12 : Every Day a Little Death
第12集: 每天都有小小的死亡
Death had come once again to Wisteria Lane.
(死神又一次降临了Wisteria Lane)
I'm afraid I have some bad news for you.
实在抱歉我要告诉你一个坏消息
We found your sister's body.
我们找到了你姐姐的尸体
Word of the tragedy would soon spread throughout the neighborhood,
(悲剧的消息会很快在邻里散布开)
but for now, people went about their lives as they always did
(但现在人们过着和往常一样的生活
- blissfully unaware.
- 充满喜悦地毫不知情)
Hello. Anybody home?
你好. 有人在吗?
In the kitchen.
我在厨房
Good news.
有个好消息
I finished my book, so I thought to celebrate, you could take me out to lunch.
我看完了我的书, 所以我想庆祝一下 你可以带我出去吃午饭
Hey, Susan.
嗨, Susan
Uh, can we do a rain check?
我们改天好吗?
Edie and I are just looking over the plans to rebuild her house.
Edie和我正在检查重造她房子的计划
My insurance company's finally cutting my check next week,
我的保险公司终于在下周付我钱了
and there's only one plumber I want.
只有一个管道工是我想要的
So don't expect to see this guy for a few months.
所以在以后几个月里都别想见这家伙了
I'm going to be riding him hard.
我会好好管教他的
Well, if anybody can go the distance, he can. I should know.
如果说有任何人能坚持到底, 他能 我应该知道
See ya.
回见
Uh, Mike?
嗯, Mike?
Mike?
We're on the clock.
我们赶时间呢
Hey, Felicia. What's up?
嗨, Felicia. 什么事?
Edie?
They found Martha.
他们找到Martha了
Here. Blow. Good. All right.
喔, 好, 好的
Come on. This is going to be fun. Follow me.
来吧. 这会很有趣的. 跟我来
Excuse me.
不好意思
Yeah?
怎么了?
You can't do that.
你不能那么做
I'm here for the 10:00 A.M. Yoga meditation class.
我来参加上午10点的瑜珈冥想课
Unfortunately, the day care center's full.
不好意思, 日托中心满了
Yeah, I noticed that, but every time I come here, it's full.
是啊, 我注意到了, 但我每次来都是满的
It's a popular class. And the other moms come early.
那课很热门, 而且其它的妈妈来得更早
Look, all I can tell you is plan ahead next time.
你看, 我能告诉你的就是下次早点来
Uh, Lauren, I'm a mother of four.
Lauren, 我是四个孩子的母亲
Today I had to get up at 5:00,
今天我不得不5点起床
make lunches, make breakfast, drop the twins off at school,
做中饭, 做早饭, 送双胞胎上学
and get across town lugging a baby and a sick child.
拖着一个生病的孩子和一个婴儿穿越城市
Telling me to plan ahead is like telling me to sprout wings,
要我再早点来就像是要我长出翅膀
and it's things like being told to plan ahead that make me so crazy
诸如此类的事情已经让我的头都大了
that yoga is the only thing that relaxes me,
瑜珈是唯一能使我放松的
except I show up here, and I can't get in, and you tell me to plan ahead.
但我来到这儿却不能进去 而你要我再早点来
It's a vicious cycle.
那是个恶性循环
See how that works?
明白了吧?
I get it.
我明白了
But if I broke the rules for you, I'd have to break them for the other moms, too,
但如果我因为你而违规 那么我也要为其它的妈妈违规
and then the moms who actually followed the rules would get all pissed at me,
而那些遵守规则的妈妈就会对我很生气
and then I'd have to get pissy right back,
然后我也会变得很生气
and before you know it, I don't have time to read my magazine.
在你知道前, 我没有时间看杂志了
See how that works?
明白了吧?
I hope someday, you have lots of children.
我希望有一天你也会有很多的孩子
Hello?
喂?
Oh, hey, Susan. Listen, I can't talk. I'm in the middle of something here that
嗨, Susan. 我现在不能和你多说 我正在
-
what?
什么?
I had a wonderful time today.
我今天很开心
Thank you. I did, too.
谢谢. 我也很开心
Sorry I can't invite you in for coffee or...
抱歉我不能请你进来喝咖啡或是...
No, I get it. Rex still lives in the house. It would be awkward.
不, 我明白. Rex还住在家里 那会很尴尬
Yeah, and I would rather cut off my hand than hurt his feelings.
是啊, 我宁愿切掉我的手也不愿 伤害他的感情
It'll, um... it'll be a lot easier once he gets well enough to move out.
那个, 嗯... 一旦他康复到可以搬出去了 就会变得轻松很多
So do you want to have lunch tomorrow?
那么明天一起吃中饭吗?
I'd love to.
乐意至极
Okay. Wow.
好的. 太好了
Pick me up at 1:00, and we'll do something fun.
一点来接我, 我们找些乐子
I'll see you then.
到时候见
Okay. Oh, packages.
好的. 哦, 包裹
O h.
哦
Thank you.
谢谢
Hello.
喂
Oh, hi, Lynette.
哦, 嗨, Lynette
What?
什么?
Sir, watch your head.
先生, 当心头
Hi, honey.
嗨, 亲爱的
Welcome home.
欢迎回家
Thanks, guys.
谢谢
Take it easy.
慢走
Come on, honey. Let's celebrate.
来吧, 亲爱的, 让我们庆祝一下
Sorry it's the cheap stuff. I had to economize.
不好意思那是便宜货, 我得节约开支
But now that you're back, we can restock the wine cellar.
但现在你回来了, 我们能重新储存酒窖了
Let's toast.
干杯
It's very good to be back.
回家感觉真好
What's that?
那是什么?
It transmits to this
它发送信号到这儿
- my electronic monitoring device.
- 我的电子监控系统
Didn't the lawyer tell you?
律师没告诉你吗?
Tell me what?
告诉我什么?
I'm on house arrest. It's a condition of my bail.
我在被软禁, 这是保释的条件之一
Uh, No. No, he neglected to tell me that.
哦, 不, 不, 他忘了告诉我
Yeah, if I move more than 100 feet from that telephone, an alarm sounds.
如果我离开那个电话100英尺远 警报器就会响
If I keep going, it transmits a signal to the FBI, and I'm back in jail.
如果我继续离开, 它会传送信号到 联邦调查局, 那么我又进去了
But how are you going to work?
那你怎么工作啊?
I can't. I can't do anything.
我不能. 我什么都不能做
Uh, no, no, no. That's unreasonable.
哦, 不, 不, 不, 那太不合理了
What do they expect us to do for money?
他们让我们怎么赚钱啊?
Well, the lawyer's working on unfreezing the accounts.
律师正在努力解冻账户
And in the meantime, I mean, haven't you been booking modeling jobs?
另外, 我说, 你不是在接模特工作吗?
Carlos, this is not like New York where I made thousands of dollars a day modeling haute couture.
Carlos, 那可不像是我在纽约为高级女装 做模特时一天能赚上千美元那样
I'm doing boat shows.
我在做船展
I spend eight hours a day doing this.
每天像这样工作8小时
Well, I'd buy two boats from you.
那我从你那儿买两条船
Come on.
拜托
Where's my toast?
不为我干杯了吗?
Welcome home.
欢迎回家
Hello.
喂
If you find anything in your sister's belongings that might shed some light on her death
如果你从你姐姐的物品里找到任何 可能对她的死因有线索的东西
letters or a datebook, please call me immediately.
信或者记事册, 请立即打电话给我
I believe she did keep a diary or something. I'll look around for it.
我相信她曾经在写日记, 我找找看
Look at them all
看看他们
-- vultures, pretending to care, when all they really want are the sordid details.
一群秃鹫, 假装关心 而他们真正想要的是肮脏的详情
I don't know. I think they just want to show their support.
我不知道. 我想他们只是想要 表现他们的支持
Please. Human beings feed on misery.
拜托. 人类以悲惨为食
Well, we might as well give the people what they want.
我们最好给他们那些他们想要的东西
Hello.
大家好
I want to thank you all for coming out here and expressing your genuine sorrow and disbelief.
我想对你们大家的到来和表现出的 真诚悲伤和不信表示感谢
My sister Martha would have been so touched.
我姐姐Martha会很感动的
I know that many of you have questions.
我知道你们中的很多人有问题想问
I've just spoken with the police, who are still putting together the details of what happened.
我刚和警察谈过, 他们仍然在整理 事件的细节
What they do know is Martha died a violent death.
他们目前知道的是Martha是被暴力致死
Oh.
哦
Yes, I know.
是的, 我知道
It's hard to hear.
那很难令人接受
Apparently, there was a struggle.
看上去, 有过一场搏斗
They found scratching and bruising on her body, several broken bones, and traces of dirt in her lungs...
他们在她身上发现了抓痕和瘀伤 几块断了的骨头, 和肺部中的粘土...
which leads us to believe that she was still alive at the time of her burial, and probably in great pain.
这些使我们相信她是被活埋的 很有可能经受了巨大的痛苦
But the good news is there are no signs that she had been molested.
但好消息是没有迹象表明她曾被性侵犯
Now I think it's time that you return to your homes, to your loved ones.
我想你们现在应该回家 回到你们所爱的人身边去了
Oh, in lieu of a memorial service, I'll be holding an estate sale day after tomorrow.
哦, 作为纪念仪式的替代 我会在后天举办一个房产销售会
Please
请
- no personal checks.
- 不要使用私人支票
By the next morning, everyone on Wisteria Lane was aware of Martha Huber's demise...
(到第二天早上, Wisteria Lane的每个人 都知道了Martha Huber的死讯...)
- Hey, guys, check out my dead woman.
- 嗨, 伙计们, 来看看我的死女人
With no exceptions.
(无人例外)
- Okay, boys.
- 好了, 孩子们
Hey, mom.
嗨, 妈妈
You see this gum?
你们看到这口香糖了吗?
If you promise to be quiet while I am downstairs playing cards, it's all yours. Deal?
如果我在楼下玩牌的时候你们能保持安静 这就是你们的了. 成交?
- Yeah.
- 好的
Deal.
成交
Yeah, okay. That's what I like to hear. All right, good.
好的. 那正是我想听到的. 很好
I mean, what are the odds? First Mary Alice, and then Mrs. Huber?
我是说, 到底是怎么回事? 先是Mary Alice, 然后是Huber夫人
I mean, it's shocking.
真是令人震惊
Yeah, but this is different. Someone was actually murdered on our street.
是啊, 但这次不同 有人在我们街道被谋杀了
I remember talking to her right before she disappeared.
我记得就在她失踪前和她谈过
You did? What'd you talk about?
是吗? 你们谈了什么?
Oh, actually, she yelled at me for not bringing my garbage cans in.
事实上, 她因为我没有把垃圾桶拿进去 而冲我嚷嚷
I'm going to miss her.
我会想她的
Edie.
Edie
Come on in.
进来吧
Oh, you're all here.
哦, 你们都在这儿
Yeah, tuesday is poker day.
是啊, 周二是扑克日
Really? Oh, you know, I love poker.
真的? 哦, 我爱扑克
Okay, then.
好吧
Well, here's the deal.
那么, 听我说
Since the ice queen isn't doing anything to memorialize her sister,
既然那个冰女王不准备纪念她的姐姐
I have decided to carry Martha's ashes up to torch lake and scatter them myself.
我决定把Martha的骨灰带去Torch湖 并把它们撒到水里
It's where her husband proposed.
那是她丈夫向她求婚的地方
That's so sweet.
那真是太好了
I know.
是啊
So I thought that some of the neighbors could caravan up there,
所以我想也许找一些邻居一起去
and we'd have a little ceremony.
我们可以举行一个小小的仪式
I've printed out maps if anyone needs one, and the dress is semi-formal.
如果有人需要地图, 我已经印好了 服装半正规的就可以了
You know, Edie, I'd love to go, but, um, I just got back into modeling,
你知道, Edie, 我很想去 但是, 嗯, 我刚刚重新开始模特工作
You know, just for fun, and I have a gig tomorrow.
只是因为好玩, 我明天有个展览会
I can't leave them hanging.
我不能放他们的鸽子
I wish I would have known earlier. I would have arranged a sitter.
真希望我早点知道, 那我就可以找个 照看孩子的人了
Darn, I have to take Rex to his angiogram.
Darn, 我必须带Rex去拍血管造影片
Hmm.
嗯
Well, Mayer? What's your excuse?
那么, Mayer? 你的借口是什么?
Um, just, you know, busy stuff.
嗯, 就是, 你知道, 太忙了
Well, your friends are much better liars.
你的朋友们撒谎的水平可比你好
Okay, mommy's friends are gone now, and you can
好了, 妈妈的朋友们走了, 你们可以
-
Ow! Ow!
哦! 哦!
Well, yeah, I know it hurts,
是啊, 我知道那很疼
but that's what you get when you let your brothers put bubble gum in your hair
但那是你让你兄弟们把泡泡糖粘到 你头上所应得的
- pain and misery.
- 痛苦和悲惨
Are you mad at me?
你在生我的气?
Yes. Yes, I am mad at you.
是的. 是的, 我在生你的气
Ow! Ow.
哦! 哦!
And I'm also cranky. You know how you get when you haven't taken a nap?
我还很暴躁. 你们知道不睡觉的后果吧?
Well, mommies are the same way. We need our downtime, and if we don't get it
妈妈们也一样 我们需要停工期, 如果得不到
-
Sorry.
对不起
We end up saying and doing things which we don't normally do.
我们就会说着和做着通常不会做的事
Ow.
哦
And that's frustrating for me, too, 'cause I do want to be the best mommy I can be.
那也让我很沮丧, 因为我希望尽可能 成为最好的妈妈
I think you're the best mommy in the world.
我想你是世界上最好的妈妈
Well, that's sweet of you, but... it's not exactly true.
那真中听, 但... 那个不是真的
I was so afraid when I suggested a picnic that you'd make fun of me,
我很担心如果我建议野餐, 你会取笑我
But I just think it's such a lovely, old-fashioned way to spend an afternoon.
但我想那样过一下午会多么可爱和老式
Well, as it happens, I'm an old-fashioned kind of guy.
我碰巧是个老式的人
Oh, and we got so lucky with the weather. It's just absolutely
而且天气也很好, 那绝对是
-
You know, your lunch hour's almost up.
你的午饭时间快结束了
We probably should be getting you back to the pharmacy.
你该回药房去了
Wait.
等等
I've had such a good time these last few days, I just want to show my appreciation.
过去几天里我是如此的快乐 我只是想表示我的感激
Another gift? I hope it's not another orchid. They're so expensive.
另一个礼物? 希望不再是兰花了 它们太贵了
Relax. This didn't cost me a dime.
没事. 这个我没花钱
Okay.
好的
George, you shouldn't have.
George, 你不必这样
This... is a 9-millimeter luger p08.
这个... 是一把9毫米鲁格尔P08手枪
From the moment you said you were in the NRA, I knew I wanted to give it to you.
当你说你曾在NRA时, 我就知道我想把它给你
I can't accept this, George.
我不能接受这个, George
This is an antique. It's too valuable.
这是个古董. 它太珍贵了
It's okay. My grandpa left it to me.
没关系. 我爷爷留给我的
It was surrendered to him by a soldier during World War II,
那是二战时一个士兵投降了交给他的
and since I don't know how to shoot...
而且我也不知道怎么开枪...
It's so lovely.
它真可爱
I mean, look at that handle. Is that mother-of-pearl?
看看那枪柄, 那是珍珠之母吗?
I think so. Only the officers' models had that.
我想是的. 只有军官用的那种有那个
Do you really like it?
你真的喜欢它?
Oh, absolutely.
当然了
Oh, George. This is just so much better than an orchid.
哦, George, 这比兰花要好多了
Hi. I'm Susan Mayer.
嗨. 我是Susan Mayer
I saw you from across the street. I thought you might need a hand.
我在街那头看到你, 我想也许你需要帮助
No thanks.
不用了, 谢谢
I-I'm sorry for what happened.
我对所发生的事感到难过
It must be really hard, not knowing who did it or why.
不知道凶手或动机的确让人很难过
You must feel helpless.
你肯定觉得无助
A bit.
有一点
I'm hoping her journals will provide some insight.
我希望她的日记能提供一些线索
Journals.
日记
Yes, Martha kept them for years.
是的, Martha写了很多年了
So she must have written a lot of things in them.
那么她肯定在里面写了很多东西
Every mundane detail of her life.
她生活中的每一件琐事
And everyone else's, for that matter.
另外, 还有其他每个人的
The police want to see them,
警察想要看它们
but I'm stalling them till I have a chance to read through them first myself.
但我会阻挠他们直到我先看完一遍
Wouldn't want any embarrassing family secrets getting out.
我可不想有家丑外泄
That's smart. That's
很聪明. 那样
- that's good.
- 那样很好
That's good to hear.
那听上去很好
I am so screwed.
我完了
Mom, calm down.
妈妈, 冷静下来
Everything about the fire and the measuring cup is going to be in that journal.
所有关于那场大火和量杯的事情 都会在那日记里
Everyone is going to think I'm an arsonist.
每个人都会认为我是个纵火犯
It may not be as bad as it looks.
也许并不像看上去那么糟
What, you think there's a chance Mrs. Huber didn't write about it in her journal?
什么, 你觉得Huber夫人有可能 不把它写在日记里吗?
Please. It's great dirt. I even put it in my journal.
拜托.  那可是猛料 我自己都把它写在日记里了
You're going to have to get to Mrs. Britt and come clean, convince her it was an accident.
你应该去找Britt夫人说明一切 说服她那是一场意外
If she doesn't press charges, the police will probably just let it go.
如果她不上诉, 警察很可能不会追究的
Are you high? Edie hates me.
有没有搞错啊? Edie讨厌我
That's why you're going to grovel at her feet and beg forgiveness.
所以你要向她卑躬屈膝乞求她的原谅
That's right.
对的
You're going to have to suck up to Edie Britt.
你必须去拍Edie Britt的马屁
Hey, Mike.
嗨, Mike
As you can probably see by now, I took back my money
你现在应该看到了, 我拿回了我的钱
and what little information you managed to dig up on your neighbors.
和你从邻居们那儿打探到的那点信息
Your replacement's going to need it.
你的替代者会需要的
Pack up and move on with your life. Sorry for the mess.
收拾东西继续你的生活吧 不好意思把你的房子弄乱了
We're here.
我们到了
10 minutes early. Sign me up?
提前了10分钟, 我能上课了?
You just missed the rush. Sorry.
你刚好错过了. 不好意思
No, no. I-I planned ahead.
不, 不, 我提早来了
We're
我们
- we're 10 minutes early.
- 我们提前10分钟了
Oh, my god.
上帝啊
What?
什么?
When you said you had a sick child, I had no idea.
当你说你有个生病的孩子, 我没注意到
How long has it been?
病了多长时间了?
Uh, just kind of snuck up on us.
嗯, 就是时不时地发作
And he's so young, too. God, it just breaks my heart.
他还那么小, 天啊, 这太令我伤心了
Oh.
哦
No, see, here's the thing
你看, 其实是这样的
You go ahead into class. I'll find room for your kids.
你去上课, 我给你的孩子们找个房间
Okay.
好的
Hey, Edie.
嗨, Edie
Susan.
Susan
Boy, I've got to say, I envy you.
我不得不说, 我妒忌你
In the name of god, why?
看在上帝的份上, 为什么?
Well, you get to build your dream house
你可以造你梦想的房子
- for free.
- 免费地
I mean, in a weird way, your house burning down was really a good thing.
我的意思是, 从一个怪异的角度看 你房子被烧其实是件好事
There's nothing good about it.
那事没什么好的
I can't replace the memories, the photographs, the
我不能替换我的记忆, 我的照片, 我的
- is there something you want?
- 你有什么事吗?
Okay, here's the deal, Edie
好吧, 是这样的, Edie
-
I
我
- I
- 我
-
Spit it out already. I'm busy.
快说吧, 我很忙
I just wanted to see how you were holding up.
我只是想来看看你情况怎么样
You know, with Mrs. Huber and everything.
你知道, Huber夫人, 以及所有的事情
My best friend was murdered and stuffed into a garbage bag,
我最好的朋友被谋杀了 还被塞进了一个垃圾袋
and nobody cares enough to... go with me to spread her ashes.
甚至没人愿意... 和我一起去撒她的骨灰
I'll go with you, Edie.
我和你一起去, Edie
Hey.
嗨
Oh, thank god. I'm starving.
谢天谢地, 我饿死了
Well, dig in. I am way too tired to eat.
自己拿吧, 我都累得吃不下东西了
Hey. I'm sorry. Come here.
嗨. 对不起. 过来这儿
Mm?
嗯?
So did you get to go by the hospital, visit mama?
你去医院看望过妈妈吗?
I worked 10 hours today.
我今天工作了10小时
I'll go by tomorrow. She doesn't even know when I'm there.
明天去. 她都不知道我在那儿
She's going to wake up soon, I know it.
她很快就会醒了, 我知道
And you know what would make her really happy?
你知道什么会让她真正开心?
Oh, god, if you say a grandchild, so help me, Carlos
哦, 天啊, 如果你想说孙子女 那么帮帮我, Carlos
-
Gabrielle, please.
Gabrielle, 拜托
No, you promised
不, 你答应的
- no babies.
- 不要孩子
Things change.
事情会改变的
Yeah, I know. The feds towed away my maserati, my husband is
我知道. 联邦调查局拖走我的Maserati车 我丈夫是
- is a felon,
- 是个重罪犯
and I spend my days getting groped by fat tractor salesmen at trade shows.
而那些肥胖的拖拉机销售员的眼睛 天天在贸易展上吃我的豆腐
I am well aware things change.
我很清楚事情的改变
A baby is solid, a constant.
孩子是家庭牢固的纽带
And who's going to be changing the diapers when you're pumping iron in a federal prison? Huh?
那么在你蹲联邦大牢的时候 谁来换尿片啊? 哼?
I like my lifestyle, and I don't want you to kill it.
我喜欢我的生活方式, 不想被你抹杀
Well, look around, Gabrielle. It's already dead,
看看周围这一切, Gabrielle 那种生活方式已经没了
and there's nothing you can control.
没有什么是你能控制的了
Maybe, but having a baby?
也许吧, 但是生个孩子?
That I can control.
我可以控制
You I can control.
我可以控制你
Hey, you can't talk to me like that. I'm still the man of this house.
嗨, 你不能用那种口气和我说话 我依然是一家之主
Oh, really?
真的?
The man of the house?
一家之主?
Don't walk away from me.
别走开
Hey, hey, my food.
嗨, 嗨, 我的食物
Gabrielle! Come back here right now!
Gabrielle!  给我回来!
Hey!
嗨!
I wouldn't go too much farther. You're going to end up back in prison.
我不会再走太远了. 你会重新回到监狱去的
Damn it, Gabrielle, get inside now!
该死的, Gabrielle, 快点进来!
Hey, I waited all day for that!
为了那个我等了整整一天!
Mmm, it's perfect.
太棒了
Crispy and burnt on the outside, but nice and steamy on the inside.
外皮松脆焦黄, 里面的肉鲜嫩多汁
You're the man of the house? You can't even leave it.
你是一家之主? 你甚至都无法离开
I love this.
我喜欢这样
It's like a little adventure. I've never fired a gun before.
这像是个小小的冒险. 我以前从未开过枪
The memory of this night will stay with you forever.
今晚的回忆将永远伴随着你
Really?
是吗?
Oh, yeah. You always remember your first time.
是啊. 你永远记得你的第一次
God, I hope I brought enough bullets.
天啊, 希望我带够了子弹
You know, Bree, I
Bree, 我
- I can't tell you what these last few days have meant to me.
- 我不知道怎么告诉你 过去几天对于我的意义
Finally getting out of the house and trying new things.
终于走出家门, 尝试新的东西
Oh. Well, we sure have had some fun.
哦, 我们的确很开心
No, no, it's
不, 不, 那
- it's more than that.
- 那不仅于此
I'm starting to forget what it feels like to be lonely.
我开始忘记孤独的感觉
Oh, George, that's so sweet.
哦, George, 你太好了
Now come on. Let's go shoot something.
来吧. 让我们开始吧
Now, before I fire a handgun, I like to go over a few of the basics just to make sure I'm ready, okay?
在我开枪之前, 我想复习下一些要点 确保我准备就绪, 好吗?
So number one, strong stance.
一, 摆好架势
Two, high hand grasp.
二, 一手托枪柄
Three, hard grip.
三, 紧握把手
Four, front sight.
四, 正视前方
Five, release the safety, and then squeeze the trigger slowly.
五, 拉保险, 然后慢慢地扣扳机
What's a high hand grasp?
什么是一手托枪柄?
Here. Take the gun.
来. 拿着枪
Okay, now, when you're firing a semiautomatic,
好, 当你发射半自动手枪时
you want the web of your hand all the way up against the edge of the backstrap.
你要把你的整个手掌紧贴在垫座的边缘
What is that perfume you're wearing?
你用的哪种香水?
Uh, I'm not wearing perfume.
我没用香水
Are you sure? Because you smell amazing.
你确定? 因为你闻起来棒极了
Oh, I was making macaroons before I left the house.
哦, 离家之前我在做蛋白杏仁饼干
Okay, now, I want you to hold the gun like you're holding a beautiful white dove.
现在, 我希望你能像 握着一只漂亮的白鸽那样握着这支枪
Hold it firmly enough that it can't fly away, but not so firmly that you can kill it. Got it?
握得紧到它不会脱手 但不要拼命地握住. 明白?
I think so.
我想是的
Now all you have to do is take a deep breath and squeeze the trigger.
现在你要做的就是深呼吸并扣扳机
George!
Oh! Oh, George!
哦! George!
Oh, my god! Are you okay?
哦, 上帝啊! 你没事吧?
Oh, George! I'm sorry!
哦, George! 真对不起!
Hey.
嗨
Hey, George.
嗨, George
I'm so sorry you lost your toe.
真对不起让你没了个脚趾
The doctor said it's the middle one, so your balance shouldn't be affected.
医生说是中间的那个 所以你的平衡感不会受到影响
I mean, this really won't change your life one little bit.
我是说, 这一点都不会改变你的生活
Please say something.
拜托, 说些什么吧
I've always dreamed that before I died,
我一直梦到在我死之前
I would get to kiss a truly beautiful woman.
我能吻一个真正美丽的女人
I finally get the chance, and I end up blowing off a toe.
我终于有了这样的机会 但却被炸掉了一个脚趾
I'm not surprised.
我不感到吃惊
This type of thing always happens to me, and I
我总是会发生这样的事 我
- I know I'll get over it.
- 我知道我会没事的
But the thing that I don't think I'll ever get over
但让我无法释怀的是
is that when I did kiss you, you pulled away from me.
当我吻你的时候, 你离开了我
Why did you do that, Bree?
你为什么那么做, Bree?
I was just caught off-guard.
我只是被你的出奇不意吓到了
But we're dating.
但我们在约会啊
Why would it be so surprising I would try to kiss you?
为什么我想吻你会让你那么吃惊呢?
I'm still married to Rex. I mean, we're not even legally separated yet.
我仍然是Rex的妻子. 我们还没真正 法律意义上的分居
He cheated on you.
他背叛了你
You said you were going to hate him forever.
你说你会永远恨他
You shouldn't listen to a woman who's just had her heart broken.
你不应该听信一个刚刚心碎了的女人的话
We tend to lie.
我们会撒谎
'Cause I think we're already late. Hi. Sorry.
因为我想我们已经太迟了. 嗨. 不好意思
Lynette knew serious illness was not a matter to be treated lightly.
(Lynette知道重病不是轻易能应对的)
- Come here.
- 过来
What are you doing?
你干什么呢?
I'm just picking up my sick, poor, little baby boy. All right, here. There. Okay. Come on.
我只是抱起我生病了的可怜的小男孩 好, 这样. 来吧
But making her yoga class was a matter of life and death.
(但是参加瑜珈课是至关重要的事)
Sorry. Sorry.
对不起. 对不起
Excuse me. Excuse me.
不好意思. 不好意思
Hey, Lauren, hi.
嗨, Lauren
We had a really rough morning.
我们经历了一个难熬的早上
Don't give it another thought.
别再想它了
I bet you were a cheerleader in high school, weren't you?
我打赌你在高中时是拉拉队队长 不是吗?
My junior year. How'd you know?
第一年时. 你怎么知道?
Girls like you were always cheerleaders.
像你那样的女孩子都是拉拉队队长
Clear skin, honor roll, popular.
背景清白, 优等学生, 受欢迎
In high school, I was the girl that hung out with the freaks on the loading dock and smoked.
在高中时, 我是那种和码头上的怪家伙们 瞎混而且还抽烟的女孩
Everyone hated us.
大家都讨厌我们
Well, you know high school. Thank god we leave that behind.
你知道高中时是怎么样的 感谢上帝那都过去了
See, I don't think we do.
我并不那么认为
I'm still the outsider that doesn't get invited to the cool parties,
我依然是不被邀请参加派对的离群者
and you're still the perky cheerleader who thinks that she can pull the wool over everyone's eyes.
你依然是那个得意的拉拉队队长 以为自己可以蒙蔽每个人
What?
什么?
You came on this trip, paid for the gas, and look at you.
你参加这次旅行, 付汽油费, 看看你自己
You're changing this flat when you know I have auto club.
你知道我参加了汽车俱乐部 可你还帮我换漏气的轮胎
You want something from me.
你想从我这儿得到什么
I just know Mrs. Huber's death's been hard on you. I want to help.
我知道Huber夫人的死让你很难过 我只想帮你
That's a lie.
你撒谎
Why would you think I was lying?
为什么你认为我在撒谎?
Because we're still in high school.
因为我们依然在高中时
The old rules apply.
那些老规则依然有效
The cool kids only want to talk to the freaks when they need something.
受欢迎的孩子只在他们需要某些东西时 才和怪孩子们讲话
Now, you're not getting back in my car until you tell me what it is that you want.
除非你现在告诉我你的目的 不然你别想坐我的车
Okay. Look, uh, I
好的. 你看, 嗯, 我
-
I just haven't always treated you well, and I want to make amends.
我一直没有好好对待你, 我想补偿
I still think you're full of crap, but we don't have time to debate this.
我认为你还是在撒谎 但我们没时间争论这个了
You know, for what it's worth, I would have talked to you in high school.
尽管可能用处不大, 但我想 我应该在高中时就和你说话的
Of all the lies you've told...
在你撒过的所有谎里...
That's the worst.
那是最烂的一个
Single malt?
单片麦芽?
Have a seat. Take a load off.
请坐. 休息会儿
I want it all back.
我想要回所有的东西
My maps, pictures, my gun... and the money.
我的地图, 照片, 我的枪... 还有钱
Oh, my money, you mean.
哦, 你是说, 我的钱
You are never going to get somebody who cares as much about finding deirdre as I do.
你找不到第二个 像我这样期望找到Deirdre的人了
Why, because you loved her so much?
为什么, 因为你那么爱她?
You abandoned her, remember?
你抛弃了她, 不记得了?
You saved yourself, found yourself a nice, safe wife, and you left my daughter to rot,
你保全了自己, 找了个安全的好妻子 而留下我的女儿走向毁灭
so forgive me if I question your level of commitment.
所以如果我怀疑你没有尽力, 请原谅我
I need to do this.
我必须这么做
Why are you fighting me?
你为什么要和我吵架?
Because you haven't been moving fast enough, and I'm running out of time.
因为你的进度不够快, 而我快没时间了
What do you mean?
什么意思?
It seems I have a tumor.
我好像长了个瘤
Apparently, it's pressing on my brain.
它似乎正在压迫我的大脑
I'm going to die, and I'd like to know what happened to my daughter before I do.
我要死了, 但在死之前我要知道 我女儿到底出了什么事
Oh, that was the best class ever. I just feel terrific. Thank you.
哦, 那是最好的班级了. 太棒了. 谢谢
Oh, Lynette, this is my friend Callie.
Lynette, 这是我朋友Callie
- Hi.
- 嗨
Hi.
嗨
She wanted to meet Parker.
她想见见Parker
Oh, really? Why?
真的吗? 为什么?
I'm a survivor.
我是个幸存者
Breast cancer. About six years ago.
乳腺癌. 大约是6年前
Can I hug your son?
我能拥抱一下你的儿子吗?
Sure.
当然
I know exactly what you're going through, but you're going to be brave, okay?
我很明白你正在经受的一切 但你要勇敢一点, 好吗?
And you are going to survive this, because you are a tough little soldier.
你会活下来的, 因为你是个勇敢的小战士
Mommy, am I dying?
妈妈, 我要死了吗?
No. You're not dying.
不, 你不会死的
People just think that because I shaved your head.
我剃了你的头发所以人们这么想
You shaved his head?
你剃了他的头发?
Yeah, my brothers put bubble gum in my hair.
是的, 我的兄弟们把泡泡糖粘到我的头发上
Sorry.
对不起
Excuse me.
失陪
And just like that,
(就那样)
Lynette realized the road to enlightenment and spiritual well-being was now closed to her.
(Lynette意识到 通向轻松和精神愉快的门合上了)
- Shanta Yoga Center-
(- Shanta瑜珈中心-)
Oh, George. What
哦, George, 真是
- w-what a surprise.
- 没想到是你
See, uh, I've been doing a lot of thinking since we talked at the hospital,
我们在医院谈过之后我想了很多
and...
然后...
and?
然后?
Bree, I don't care what we call it.
Bree, 我不在乎我们怎么看待它
We can call it dating, we can call it hanging out. Whatever it is, I just want to be with you.
它可以是约会, 也可以是消磨时间 不管怎样, 我只想和你在一起
See, uh, I really need our friendship back.
我真的想挽回我们的朋友关系
I don't think that would be wise.
我认为那是不明智的
Why not?
为什么?
Well, I mean, wouldn't you keep hoping that, in time,
我的意思是, 你是不是一直期望将来
I would feel the same way about you as you feel about me?
我会对你有像你对我那样的感觉?
Maybe.
也许吧
Oh, George.
哦, George
I wish you wouldn't say "oh, George" like that,
我希望你不要以那种口气说“哦, George”
like I'm so pathetic for even thinking that you could love me someday.
好像我连有某天你会爱我的想法都很可怜
I don't think you're pathetic. It's just that
我没有认为你很可怜. 只是
-
I can't.
我不能
Aw, jeez.
天啊
Oh, George, please don't go.
哦, George, 请别走
Why can't we talk this over?
我们为什么不能好好商量一下呢?
- George
-
Don't
不要
- ugh!
- 啊!
Oh, my god.
上帝啊
- Oh, George, here,
- 哦, George, 这儿
Take
来
- get away from me!
- 离我远点!
Lean on me.
靠着我
I don't need you.
我不需要你
I don't need anybody!
我不需要任何人!
You know, honey, tonight's the last night of the boat show.
你知道, 亲爱的, 今晚是船展的最后一天
We'll be able to spend some time together before the home and garden thing next week.
我们可以在家门口待一会儿 下礼拜做些园艺活
Carlos?
I'm going to jail, and you're not going to be here when I get back.
我会回监狱, 当我回来时你不会在这儿
What?
什么?
It's true, and I won't blame you.
是真的, 我不怪你
Don't talk like that. Everything's going to be fine.
别那么说, 一切都会好起来的
We're going to sort this mess out, and you're going to be back on top again.
我们会渡过这一关, 你会东山再起
Gabby, they could find me guilty on every charge.
Gabby, 他们可以在任何一项上定我的罪
I could go to prison for five years.
我会在牢里待五年
We'd probably have to sell the house, you'd have to keep working
我们很可能需要卖掉这房子 而你必须继续工作
-
Okay, Carlos
好的, Carlos
-
If that happens, can you promise you won't ever leave?
如果那样的事发生了, 你能答应不离开吗?
I promise.
我答应你
I got to go.
我要走了
This is far enough.
这样够远了
Do you need help with the container?
你要我帮你打开那个容器吗?
No, I got it open. I'm good.
不用了, 打开了的, 我没事
So what are you waiting for?
你在等什么啊?
I just need a moment, okay?
我只是需要点时间, 可以吗?
Oh, of course. Take your time.
当然可以, 请随意
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
No, I'm just so grateful.
没事, 我真是很感激
I know. I-I know. Mrs. Huber was a good friend to you.
我明白. 我-我明白 Huber夫人是你的好朋友
I'm not talking about Martha.
我不是说Martha
I'm grateful to you.
我很感激你
Me?
我?
Yeah, I've been such a bitch to you over the years, and...
我这些年来一直没有好好对你, 而...
Here you are, rowing me out to dump her ashes.
你现在为我划船来撒骨灰
Well, it's
那
- it's really no
- 那真的
- no big deal.
- 没什么大不了的
Yes, it is.
那很重要
You stepped up when nobody else would, and --
你在别人都不愿意的情况下挺身而出
and here I am, thinking you have an ulterior motive.
而我还在怀疑你有什么隐秘的企图
Oh. God, Susan, you're such a good person.
天啊, Susan, 你真是个好人
And I'm such a bitch.
而我是这么的坏
Oh, Edie, you're not that bad, and
Edie, 你没那么坏, 而且
- and
- 而且
- and believe me,
- 而且相信我
I'm
我
- I'm not that good.
- 我也没那么好
Oh, yes, you are.
不, 你就是那么好
Oh, please don't do this.
请别这么说
You know, Martha may be gone...
Martha过世了...
But the good lord above has shown me that I'm not alone.
但仁慈的主指引我发现我并不孤单
I am so grateful that I still have a true friend.
我真高兴还有一个真正的朋友
Thank you, Susan.
谢谢你, Susan
Edie, I burned your house down.
Edie, 我烧了你的房子
Huh?
什么?
I was scared that you were sleeping with Mike, and so I let myself in, and I-I snuck around.
我担心你和Mike上床了 所以我进入你的房子, 偷偷地到处察看
I-I accidentally knocked a candle over, and the whole
我不小心碰倒了一个蜡烛 然后整个
- just
- 就
- I'm so sorry.
- 真是对不起
Can you ever forgive me?
你会原谅我吗?
Row me back.
划回去
Now.
快点
I'm sorry about before
我真抱歉刚才
- shoving you.
- 推了你
I didn't mean
我不是故意
- I'm not going to break.
- 我骨头不会断的
I'm sorry, too.
我也很抱歉
Questioning your commitment, your guts
怀疑你对此事的投入, 你的勇气
-
I know better than that.
我应该知道的
Yeah. You should.
是啊, 你应该知道
I keep this with me all the time to remind me why I'm there.
我一直带着它 以此提醒自己为什么在这里
If it turns out someone hurt her, I want them dead.
如果最终查明是有人伤害了她 我要他们血债血偿
We need to be sure before we do anything.
我们在有所行动前必须确认无误
Well, when you're sure,
好吧, 等你确定了以后
I know I can trust you to take care of it.
我知道你能处理好
After all, you already killed for her once.
毕竟你已经为她杀过人
Yeah, is this the pharmacy?
喂, 是药房吗?
My wife asked me to call. She lost her prescription.
我妻子让我打电话来, 她弄丢了处方
Gabrielle Solis.
Gabrielle Solis
Yeah, the birth-control pills.
是的, 避孕药
Great, great. She'll be very relieved.
很好, 很好, 她会很安心的
Can she get enough for a couple months?
能一次买够几个月用的吗?
Yeah, that's right. Better safe than sorry.
是的, 事前安全好过事后后悔
Thanks a lot.
非常感谢
Oh, do you guys deliver?
哦, 你们送货上门吗?
Edie, please talk to me.
Edie, 说说话啊
I've been thinking about this for the last 90 miles, and you don't have to forgive me.
在刚才的90英里路里我一直在想 你不必原谅我
You can go to the police, kick me.
你可以去警察局告我
You can burn my house down.
你可以烧了我的房子
You just have to know that I am so racked with guilt,
只是你要知道我被罪恶感煎熬
I don't think it's possible for me to suffer any more than I'm already suffering.
我想我不可能比现在更难过了
Boy, I'd like to put that theory to the test.
哦, 我想试试看你说的是不是真的
Well... whatever you want to do, Edie.
那么... 任何事情都可以, Edie
Just know that I'm sorry.
只要你知道我很抱歉
I'm not going to the police.
我不会去警察局告你
You're not?
你不会去吗?
No.
不会
The insurance company will just want to investigate, and it'll delay my check.
保险公司会想要调查, 那会延迟我的支票
Thank you.
谢谢你
But...
但是...
there is something I want you to do for me.
我想要你为我做些事
Of course. Anything.
当然. 任何事都可以
You name it. What?
你说吧. 什么事?
I want to be invited to your poker game.
我想要被邀请参加你们的扑克游戏
Our poker games?
我们的扑克游戏?
I'm not saying I'll go, and I'm not saying that you and your little friends have to be nice to me,
我没说我要参加, 我也没说 你和你的那些小伙伴要对我好一点
but every once in a while, yeah, it'd be nice to be asked.
不过时不时地, 嗯, 被邀请也很愉快
Well, uh, we meet on tuesdays, and it's potluck lunch. Everybody has to bring something.
嗯, 我们周二见面, 中饭是家常便饭 每个人都要带些东西
I'm not bringing anything.
我不会带任何东西
Oh, you don't have to.
哦, 你不必带
Well, this is good.
那很好
Thank you.
谢谢
I guess I should go take a shower and...
我想我该去洗个淋浴...
wash Mrs. Huber off me.
把Huber夫人从身上洗掉
Hold it.
等一下
I can't stand the thought of Martha's ashes going down some sewer drain.
想到Huber夫人将被冲到下水道去 真是让我难以忍受
Well, Edie, I-I have to clean up.
Edie, 我必须清洗一下
Well, this is such a beautiful lawn.
这个草坪真漂亮
We could put her to rest right here.
我们让她在这里安睡吧
On my front lawn?
在我的前院草坪?
Why not?
为什么不?
She could spend all of eternity looking at her house and keep an eye on the neighborhood.
她可以永远地注视她的房子 还可以密切关注她的邻居
She'd like that.
她会喜欢那样的
Stand over here. I'll hose you off.
过来站这儿. 我替你冲洗
I don't think so.
我不想这样
You owe me.
你欠我的
Martha... I'm going to miss you.
Martha... 我会想你的
Death is inevitable.
(死亡无法避免)
It's a promise made to each of us at birth.
(那是一个我们出生时就许下的诺言)
But before that promise is kept, we all hope something will happen to us.
(但是在诺言兑现之前 我们都希望会有些事情发生)
Whether it's the thrill of romance...
(不管那是浪漫激情...)
Hey, come back here!
嗨, 回这儿来!
The joy of raising a family...
(养育孩子的快乐...)
I'm going to get you! I'm going to get you!
我来抓你了! 我来抓你了!
Or the anguish of great loss...
(还是巨大损失的悲痛...)
we all hope to experience something that make our lives meaningful.
(我们都希望经历一些让生命有意义的事)
But the sad fact is not all lives have meaning.
(但不幸的是并不是所有的生命都有意义)
Some people spend their time on this planet just sitting on the sidelines...
(一些人只是天天坐视旁观...)